嗨  打扰一下
Hi, excuse me.
我在找卡特福特
Yeah, I'm looking for Carter Ford.
能告诉我哪个是他吗？
Do you mind pointing him out to me?
但愿不是光头那个
I hope he's not the bald one.
身上有文身那个
Guy with the ink.
他在摆擂台  谁的挑战他都接
He's takin' all comers.
新威龙杀阵
来啊！
Come on!
粗略一算
A little back-of-the-envelope arithmetic says
威名赫赫的卡特福特已连下六城
that's six in a row for the illustrious Carter Ford.
谁想进去给他凑够七连胜？
Who wants to get in there, make it seven, huh?
谁想上场一试？
Who wants to do it?
今晚可是赢家通吃  各位
It's winner-take-all tonight, y'all.
奖金“不多”  一大桶而已
It's just a bunch of money in a bucket.
卡特福特已连下六城  谁将拿下一城？
Carter Ford's got six. Who's gonna get one?
我帮你缠绷带  双手平摊
I'm gonna tape you. Arms flat.
不用吗？
Someone step in. - No?
开始了！现在，有想再看比赛的吗？
Let's get this goin'! Now, who wants to see another fight?
-蠢货  -你玩过笼斗吗？
- Fucking guy. - You ever done this before?
这货是谁？好吧  来了个超级英雄
- Who the fuck is this? - All right, a superhero.
靠过来吧！快点
Close it up! Come on.
你知道那家伙是谁吗？
Jesus, Carter. You know who that is?
不  没门儿
Nah. Nope.
我绝不跟那家伙打  门儿都没有！
I'm not fightin' that fucking guy. No fuckin' way!
没门儿  门儿都没有！
No fuckin' way. There's no fuckin' way.
去你的
Yeah, fuck you.
我不在乎
I don't give a fuck. I'm not...
他可是那该死的家伙
- He's that fucking guy. - You ain't gonna fight for your money?
我干吗要想不开跟他打？
Why would I fight that guy?
好了  出去吧  快点
- Keep your fuckin' money! - All right, get outta here.
我不稀罕你们的臭钱！
I don't want your fuckin' money.
-你们知道他是谁吗？  -走吧
- You know who the fuck he is? - Let's go.
你们来一个我打一个  保证打得你们满地找牙
I'll fight any fuckin' one of you. I'll fuckin' beat your ass.
至于他  你们自己打去吧！
You fuckin' fight him!
我才不和那晦气的家伙打
- Get your ass back in there! - I'm not fightin' that fucking guy.
通通见鬼去吧！去你的！
You can all go fuck yourselves! Fuck you!
去你的！
Fuck you!
还有你！
Fuck you too!
操蛋！滚！-
- Fuck that shit! Bullshit! - Get out! Get out!
拿去吧  这是你的奖金
There you go. Here's your money.
-不！  -美女  规则可不是我定的
- No! Come on. - I don't make the rules, honey.
嘿！道尔顿
Hey! Dalton!
你这就想走了？
Where you goin'?
你刚刚害我损失了500块  混蛋
You just lost me 500 bucks, asshole.
你确定你想清楚了？
You sure you thought this all the way through?
嘿  你要去哪儿？
Hey, where you goin'?
不把你的刀收走吗？
You're not gonna take your knife?
该死的
Shit.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你刚刚那招虚张声势用得真漂亮
It's a nice little scam you got goin' on in there.
只须让对手知道你是谁
All you need is for the opponent to know who you are...
在那？-
Where is it?
知道你的过往  他们便会害怕得不战而降
Know your history, and then they'll be too afraid to fight.
真是聪明  伙计
- That's fuckin' brilliant, man. - Yeah.
动脑子总比动手好
Yeah, well, beats workin'.
说实话  我一开始都没认出你来
You know, it actually took me a second to recognize you.
天啊
Oh... Oh, God.
你需要救护车什么的吗？
Um, do you need a ambulance or something?
不需要
Nope.
你身上插着一把刀呢
You know you got a big-ass knife stickin' outta you?
能帮我拿着这个吗？
Can you hold this?
当然
Sure.
待会拔刀后  伤口会流血
It's gonna bleed when I take it out.
我的天啊
Oh, shit!
虽然会留下难看的疤痕
It's gonna leave a nasty scar...
但这样比较省事
but it's easier this way.
天啊  看来你经常做这种事
- Wow, it seems like you do this a lot. - Huh?
是啊
Yeah.
成功的秘诀在于耐心
Patience and a keen interest in the result...
和求胜心
that's all it takes.
我在佛罗里达群岛上
So listen, I own a roadhouse.
经营着一家路边餐馆
Out in the Florida Keys.
路边餐馆？
A roadhouse, huh?
海明威曾在那里喝过酒
Hemingway used to drink there.
你知道欧内斯特海明威吧？
You know... Ernest Hemingway?
真不错
Good for you.
我那餐馆本就是个闹哄哄的地方
It's always been a rowdy place.
大家都到店里来释放压力
People come to blow off steam.
但近期经常有不速之客光顾
But lately it's been attractin' the wrong clientele.
他们夜夜生事  把餐馆弄得一团糟
Come in every night. They trash the place.
警察根本帮不上忙
The cops are no fuckin' help.
我的保镖也跑光了
All my fuckin' bouncers have ran off.
给我
Hand me that.
总之  我最终还是决定  向外界寻求帮助
Anyway, I finally decided I needed some outside help.
我的一个朋友建议我  来找一个名叫卡特福特的人谈谈
A friend of mine suggested I come talk to some guy named Carter Ford.
确实  卡特的身手似乎挺不错的
Yeah, well... Carter seems good with his hands.
不  你更好
No, you'd be better.
我可以给你支付丰厚的薪水  周薪五千  为期一个月
I can pay you good money. 5k a week... just for a month.
我可以帮你安排个住处
And I can put you up.
我抽不出身来  抱歉
I'm all booked up. Sorry.
什么？那可是整整两万美元
'Scuse me? I mean, it's 20 grand.
从你的车来看  你应该需要那些钱
And judging by your car, you need that shit.
我喜欢我的车
Well, I like my car.
我给你的报酬  应该比你参加那个什么…
Okay, that's gotta be more than you're makin' for...
赚的要多吧
whatever the hell you call this.
你去找卡特吧
Try Carter.
至少让我发个联系电话给你
Look, at least let me text you my number.
我没有手机  所以…
I don't have a phone, so...
好吧  稍等一下
Well, hold on.
我用最原始的方式纸和笔  给你写下来
I'll write it down on a pen and paper, just like our ancestors did.
我叫弗兰基
I'm Frankie.
你考虑一下
Think about it.
祝你晚安  女士
You have a good night, ma'am.
这里不是假日酒店  伙计
This ain't the Holiday Inn, pal.
我…我这就走
I'll move it. I'm movin'.
他闪挪腾移  左摇右摆
He's movin' and a shakin'.
本杰明的攻势被卡尔维诺化解了  30秒过去了
Benjamin gets blocked by Calvino with 30 seconds down.
挑战者使出了一记右摆拳
An overhand right landed by the challenger
紧接一套左左右的组合拳…
with a straight left-left-right combination.
本杰明把冠军抬了起来  想要推开他
And Benjamin is lifting up the champion and pushing him away!
本回合还剩下16秒
There's 16 left to go in the round.
卡尔维诺出击了  他右手甩出一拳…
And now here comes Calvino. He lands a right.
他被挑战者击倒了
Couple of shots landed by the challenger.
本杰明左右出击  打出好几拳  卡尔维诺从上方和左侧
Benjamin landing some lefts and rights. Calvino hits high.
击中了挑战者  带来雷鸣般的钟声
And a left on the challenger, bringin' the thunder.
紧接着卡尔维诺用膝盖压住了对方…
And a knee to the body by Cal...
右直拳  然后用膝盖压住了对方的身体…
right hand, and then a knee to the body by...
还是算了
Maybe not.
弗兰基  3051365211
欢迎收听WYBS电台  FM106.4  佛罗里达群岛频道
WYBS 106.4 for the Florida Keys...
宛如一叶叶海上扁舟的群岛  是古巴哈瓦那的一部分
parts of Havana, Cuba, and the vessels at sea...
还有FM102.8  基韦斯特频道
and 102.8 in Key West.
你进来的路上看到弗雷德了吗？
Did you see Fred on your way in?
你说什么？
What's that?
桥上那棵树  弗雷德
Fred, the tree on the bridge?
不是主桥  而是旁边那座旧的
Not the main bridge, but the old one beside it.
历史悠久的七英里桥
The historic Seven Mile Bridge?
它就长在路中央
He grows right in the middle of the road.
你看到它了吗？
Did you see him?
恐怕没看到
I can't say that I did.
虽然整座桥都封闭了  你无法靠近它  但…
You know, that whole bridge is closed. You can't get to it...
那棵不知从哪里冒出来的老树
but big old tree just kinda pops outta nowhere.
它就是大树弗雷德
Well, that's Fred the tree.
而你…
And...
感兴趣的话  这里有一本关于它的书
got a book on him, if you're interested.
内容充满本地色彩  非常适合游客
It's full of local color and all. It's great for tourists.
顺带一提  我叫查莉
I'm Charlie, by the way.
玻璃岛书店
嘿  查莉
Hey, Charlie.
你一个人经营着这家书店吗？
You run this bookstore all on your own?
不是
No.
不过我是店主之一
I am one of the owners, though.
你怎么会来到玻璃岛？
What brings you to Glass Key?
我来这里的一家酒吧工作
I'm here to work at a bar.
当酒保？
- Bartending? - No.
-不是  -酒吧里还能有什么工作？
What other job is there at a bar?
我想酒吧的老板遇到了一点麻烦
Well, the owner's havin' a little trouble, I guess, and I'm...
我是来帮忙解决问题的
just here to clean it up.
听起来就像西部片的情节
That kinda sounds like the plot to a western.
就像…
Like...
“小镇居民请来一位英雄  帮忙整顿乌烟瘴气的酒吧”
"Local townsfolk send for a hero to help clean up the rowdy saloon."
套路你懂的
You know that crap?
查莉  你就别烦着人家了
Charlie, leave this poor man alone.
真抱歉  她整天热衷于推销书籍
Yeah, I'm sorry. She gets excited about sellin' books and trees...
大树和弗雷德什么的…  -嗨  我叫斯蒂芬
and Fred and all that... Hi, I'm Stephen.
-我叫道尔顿
- Dalton. - Mmm-hmm.
他是来这边的路边餐馆上班的
Oh, he's here to work at the Road House.
-真的吗？  -那里的老板弗兰基
- Uh... Really? - See, the owner, uh, Frankie...
她只跟我说是一家路边餐馆  却没有告诉我名字
she told me it was a roadhouse, but she never told me the name.
就叫路边餐馆
It's just the Road House.
也就是说没有…没有名字？
Oh, so no name?
没有…对
Ah, well, no, well, yeah.
可以这么说  那里就叫路边餐馆
Kinda. It's the Road House.
沿着公路向前走  过了77英里标识牌就能到
It's just up the highway, past mile marker 77.
谢谢你推荐的书  但我…
Well, thank you for the book but...
预算有限  没事
- I'm on a budget. - No, no.
你留着吧
Keep it, please.
就当我们送你的
It's on us.
谢谢
Thank you.
欢迎来到玻璃岛
Welcome to Glass Key.
谢谢  斯蒂芬
Thanks, Stephen.
77英里
路边餐馆  餐馆兼酒吧
但他们到这里还要五分钟-
But just like five more minutes till they get here.
等不了！-
I can't wait!
你们现在就要走吗？对啊，走了-
- You guys wanna go now? - Yeah, yeah, let's do it.
不  真是的…每次都这样  每次…
No! Every single time. Every...
-他在纠缠你吗？  -对  他又想讨要免费酒喝
- He's bothering you? - Yeah, he wants free drinks again.
免费个鸡毛-
You're not gettin' free shit, Reed.
一视同仁，者要钱-
You gotta fuckin' pay like everybody else, man.
好吧  我发誓  这是最后一杯了
If you... Okay. This is the last one, I swear.
-到此为止  -谢谢
- That's it. - I appreciate you.
-那就最后一杯  -最后一杯
- Last one, though. - Last one.
我保证你再也不会喝到免费酒了
You're not gettin' any more for free, I swear to God.
-我发誓  这个老流氓…  -我才17岁
- Swear to God, this bum. - 17.
好吧
- Okay. - Hiya.
可以给我一杯黑咖啡吗？
I'll get a black coffee.
我们不卖黑咖啡  抱歉
Oh, uh... Yeah, we don't have that. Sorry.
那你喝的是什么？
What're you drinkin'?
这是古巴咖啡
It's, uh, Cuban coffee.
好吧
Okay.
味道相去甚远
It's... very different.
给我来一杯吧
- Yeah. - Can I have one of those?
好的  没问题
Sure. Okay.
嘿
Hey.
我认识你
I know who you are.
你是埃尔伍德道尔顿
Elwood Dalton.
我是你的超级粉丝
Big fan, man.
你在干什么？冷静点  伙计
What you doin'? Just keep it cool, man.
我什么时候不冷静了？
When am I not cool?
我是个超级粉  你不知道他是谁-
Hey, I'm a big fan. You didn't know who he is.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you, ma'am.
哇
Yikes.
没骗你吧
Yeah.
这味道我喜欢  那就好
- I really like that. - Good.
好
Yeah.
这里真是个好地方
Nice place you got here.
好安静
Peaceful.
♪ 即使不盲目自大… ♪
♪ You don't have to be blind ♪
去你的  混蛋！
Fuck you, motherfucker!
你才是  去你的混账…
Fuck you, you piece of shit!
♪ 或拒绝现在就放弃 ♪
♪ I refuse to give up now ♪
♪ 经受住所有考验和磨难… ♪
♪ See all the trials And tribulations through ♪
♪ 只要你能做到这些 ♪
♪ If you can do all these things ♪
嘿
Hey!
♪ 即使不是王 ♪
♪ You don't have to be a king ♪
嘿！
Hey!
给我出去  伙计  滚出去
Get out, man. Go. Get the fuck out.
滚出去
Get the fuck...
-嘿  -去你的！
- Hey! - Fuck you!
你给我出去  伙计  滚出去
You're fuckin' out, man. Get the fuck out.
♪ 也能分辨是非 ♪
♪ To know right from wrong ♪
♪ 将来某一天 ♪
♪ One of these days ♪
♪ 当你听到一个声音说“来吧” ♪
♪ When you hear a voice say, "Come" ♪
♪ 你会奔向何方？ ♪
♪ Where you gonna run to? ♪
♪ 你跑到岩石上求援 ♪
♪ You're gonna run To the rock for rescue ♪
♪ 结果空无一人… ♪
♪ There will be no rock ♪
♪ 腰间挂着手枪 ♪
♪ Walkin' down the road ♪
♪ 走在大路上… ♪
♪ With your pistol in your waist ♪
这里就像个停尸房！
Wow, it's like a morgue in here.
嘿
Hey.
四号过道  清理一下
Cleanup! Aisle four.
给我滚出去  兄弟
Get the fuck outta here, bro.
窝囊废  你玩得够久了
Hey, asshole. You've been playing long enough.
该轮到我了
Give me a turn. Give me a turn.
嘿
Oh, hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-放手  放开我！  -给我来杯酒嘛
- Just let go. - Hey, get me a drink.
走吧！我没拦你-
- Let go! - I'm not holding you.
嘿！别这样！冷静点！
Hey, hey, hey, come on! Chill out.
冷静点！
Chill out! Chill out!
比利
Oh, Billy.
你就这么蠢吗？
You're that stupid?
-住手  -你还没吸取教训  是吧？
- Stop. - You didn't learn, did you?
小心我们揍死你
We'll whoop your ass.
你还没学乖吗？-还想再来个黑眼圈吗？
You didn't learn? You want another black eye?
我现在就给你再上一课  -不…
- I'll give you another one right here. - No, I don't want another one.
-你叫比利  对吧？  -对
- It's Billy, right? - Yeah.
那边有几个口渴的顾客正等着
There's some thirsty customers waitin' for you.
-我来招待这几位就好  -好的
- I can handle these gents. - Okay.
你是谁啊  微笑先生？
Who the fuck are you, Mr. Smiley?
微笑先生？是啊
- Mr. Smiley? - Yeah.
从我进来那一刻起  你就笑得像个白痴似的
You've had this idiot grin since I walked in.
你很开心吗？
So, are you happy?
你是傻子吗？
Are you stupid?
还是因为脸上挨了太多拳头？
Or get punched in the face too many times?
说实话  应该是挨了太多拳头
Honestly, it's probably the punching thing.
可以出去谈谈吗？
Can I talk to you guys outside for a second?
不了  我还有事要忙
Nah. I got some work to do.
再来一根
Another one.
外面那些是你们的摩托车  对吧？
Those are your bikes out there, right?
对  我的是右边那台红色的
Yeah. Mine's the red one on the right.
-等等  搞什么？  -等一下
- Wait, what the fuck? - Wait up.
嘿  混蛋！
Hey, asshole!
给我站住
Stop right there.
我只是想让你们到外面来
I just wanted to get you outside
以便礼貌地请你和你的朋友
so I could ask you and your friends respectfully...
礼貌地离开
to leave the premises.
我们会走的
Oh, we'll leave.
-等我宰了你之后
After I fucking kill you.
-好吧
Sure.
开打前先问一下
Uh, before we start...
你有保险吗？
do you have insurance?
什么？
What?
我指的是你的医保
Like, you have medical insurance?
覆盖的项目全吗？有牙科保险吗？
Your coverage good? Like, you have dental?
需要那些的人可不是我
Oh, ha-ha! Yeah. I'm not the one that's gonna fuckin' need it.
好吧
Okay.
-当然了
Sure.
嘿  弗兰基  -什么？
- Hey, Frankie? - Yeah?
-这附近有医院吗？
Is there a hospital nearby?
-说真的  谁在乎呢？
Literally, who gives a shit?
-废话少说  快打吧  混蛋！
Shut the fuck up and fight, asshole!
-这附近有医院吗？
Is there a hospital nearby?
会不会太远？离这里近吗？
- Is it like, too far? Is it close? - What?
离这里大概25分钟车程吧
About, like, 25 minutes, I'd say.
取决于交通状况和时间
Like, depending on the traffic, what time of day and stuff.
-莫伊
Moe?
你给我闭嘴！  -好
- Shut the fuck up! - Right.
你叫什么名字？
Hey, what's your name?
-戴尔  -戴尔
- Dell. - Dell?
你真的大可不必这样  我…
You don't have to do this, man. I... You don't...
你真的大可不必  当着所有朋友的面输给我
You don't have to lose, you're gonna lose in front of all your friends.
“当着”？
"In front of"?
他们可不只是观战的
Oh, they're not here to just watch.
-这不公平吧
Oh, well, that's hardly fair.
-人生本就不公平
Life's not fair.
-见鬼  -我刚扇了你一巴掌  -没事吧？
- I just slapped you. Are you all right? - Shit. What?
-什么…  搞什么？
- What? - What the fuck?
天啊！见鬼！
Damn! Damn!
-快  揍趴他  -快上  戴尔！
Fuck him up. Come on, do it again!
快上  戴尔！
Fuck him up!
真见鬼！
Oh, shit!
咱们就当打成平手吧
Let's call this a draw.
什么叫打成平手？
What the fuck's a draw?
类似于赢了
It's kinda like a win, man.
-我赢了？  -是平局的意思  戴尔
- Like, I win? - It's a tie, Dell.
对  你我双赢
Yeah, like, we win together, you know?
见鬼去吧！
Fuck you!
该死的
Fuck, man.
我要杀了你！
I'm gonna kill you!
天杀的
Holy fuck.
得了吧  没那么严重
Oh, come on. It's not that bad.
我想你打断我的胳膊了
I think you broke my arm.
你的胳膊确实被我打断了
I definitely broke your arm.
好消息是  这里离医院只有20分钟车程
But the good news is the hospital's only 20 minutes away.
我说的是25分钟  好吗？
Okay. I said 25. Okay?
真是的  我这样根本骑不了车  可恶
God, I don't think I can ride like this. Fuck!
-嘿  弗兰基  -什么？
Hey, Frankie?
-你有车可以借我一用吗？
- Yeah? - You got a car I could borrow?
-有是有  但你别指望用来载他们
I do, yeah, but not for them.
别这样嘛  这些人需要治疗
Come on. These guys need medical attention.
是吗？老娘我不在乎
Oh, yeah? I don't give a shit.
我要起诉你
I'm gonna sue you.
颠簸
Bump.
该死的
Shit.
我想他可能有点脑震荡
I think he's probably got a concussion...
他则是膝盖受伤  可能脱臼了
and then he's got knee damage, possibly a dislocation.
然后还有那个…就是那个…
And then the one, that one, I think needs...
谢谢你载我一程  伙计
Thanks for the ride, man.
那是你的朋友吗？
Is that one a friend of yours?
不  他只是被我打断了胳膊
Uh, no, I just broke his arm.
嘿
Hey.
在你走之前  我想谢谢你  送了这么多新患者过来
Before you go, I really wanted to say thank you for all the new patients.
不客气
Um... you're welcome.
急诊室被一群不负责任的白痴挤爆  真是喜闻乐见
I just love when my ER's packed full of irresponsible idiots.
这样一来  真正急需救助的普通人  就会求助无门
That way, the normal people with real emergencies have nowhere to go.
不过像你这种脾气暴躁
But that's not something you'd care about...
以伤害他人为乐的白痴  根本不会在乎这些
being a rage-filled dickhead who likes to hurt people for fun.
“白痴”？
"Dickhead"?
严格来说  我是为了钱才伤害他人的
Well, technically, I hurt people for money.
这能好到哪里去？
And how is that better?
好不到哪里去  我只是想澄清一下
I guess it's not. I'm just clarifying.
你知道我应该报警抓你这种人吧？
You know I'm supposed to call the cops on guys like you, right?
你确实应该报警
Well, you definitely should.
只不过他们似乎无意管治  这一带的暴脾气白痴
Only, I don't think they really care about rage-filled dickheads around these parts.
你在流血
You're bleeding.
见鬼
Oh, shit.
不  那只是…无妨
Oh, uh, no, that's just... It's fine.
让我看一下
Let me see it.
好的
All right.
看来你喜欢打架
So, you like to fight?
你赢过吗？
You ever win?
打架从来没有赢家
No one ever wins a fight.
那你为什么还要打？
Then, why do you do it?
虽然没有感染  但伤口得缝合一下
It's not infected, but I'll need to suture this.
不用了  谢谢
Oh, no, no, no. Thank you.
-为什么？
Why not?
-因为我有错在先  想付出点代价
It's my fault. I wanna pay for it.
好吧
Fine.
可以吗？
Can I?
有人把车停在应急车道-
Someone left their car in the emergency area.
请移走 车牌…-
Please move it. License plate...
-这是头孢氨苄
Cephalexin.
-不  我不需要止痛的东西
Oh, no, I don't need anything for the pain.
这是一种抗生素
It's an antibiotic.
必须服满一个周期
Do the full cycle.
医生  谢谢你
Hey, doc, thank you.
抱歉给你添了那么多麻烦
Sorry for all the trouble.
去跟我的员工说吧  他们才是今晚加班加点的人
Tell it to my staff. They're the ones with all the extra work tonight.
嘿  你在削什么？
Hey, what are you whittling?
一根棍子
A stick.
我知道  我是问你要把它削成什么
Yeah, but what's it gonna be?
一根较小的棍子
A smaller stick.
是他吗？
Is that him?
祝你晚安  女士
You have a good night, ma'am.
再次为我添的麻烦道歉
Again, I'm sorry for the trouble.
谢谢
Thanks.
对  就是他
Yeah, that's him.
就是那个家伙
That's the guy.
他运用了各种武术  马伽术
He threw in little bits of everything. What? The Krav Maga...
柔道、柔术  还有那一巴掌
judo, jujitsu, you know, like, the slap.
那是什么？苏巴克？对吧？
What's that? Subak? Right?
嘿  强击手
Hey, slugger.
给你  一周的薪水
Here it is. One week's salary.
按照你的要求以现金支付
In cash, as requested.
谢谢  不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
应该是我谢谢你
Thank you.
你这餐馆的选址真不错  弗兰基
Got a beautiful spot here, Frankie.
当然不错了
You bet your ass it's beautiful.
瞧这风景
I mean, look at this.
想象一下和心爱之人在那里把酒言欢
Imagine having a drink right there with somebody special, you know?
你甚至可以在这里结婚
Hell, you could even get married here.
还有离婚
Divorced, too.
然后再回到这里借酒浇愁
Then you can come back and drown your sorrows.
人生百态  尽在于此
I mean, it's a whole "circle of life" thing.
-多么动人的宣传演讲
Oh. That's one hell of a sales pitch.
-对
Yeah.
我知道如今的玻璃岛早已今非昔比
Look, I know the Glass Key ain't what it once was.
但…
But...
我觉得这里可以成为  一个很特别的地方
I think this place could be something really special.
可以问你一个问题吗？
Can I ask you a question?
当然
Sure.
为什么要叫“路边  餐馆”？
Why is it called the Road House?
-什么意思？
What do you mean?
-路边餐馆不是…一个词吗？
Isn't roadhouse one word?
对  这就是幽默的地方
Yeah, that's the joke.
这是一家路边餐馆
It's a roadhouse.
名字叫“路边  餐馆”  懂了吗？
But it's called the Road House. Get it?
还是一头雾水
Still unresolved.
我也不太清楚  我叔叔的幽默感比较独特
Well, I don't know. My uncle had a unique sense of humor.
对了  镇上有一家不错的旅馆
Hey, so, there's this cute hotel in town.
应该说是镇上唯一一家旅馆  但所幸还不错
I mean, it's the only hotel in town but luckily, it's cute.
这个嘛  我看到码头那边  有一艘待售的船屋
Well, you know, I saw that there was a houseboat for sale at the marina...
我打算去看一下
so I thought maybe I'd go check that out, but...
那艘破船？
That old tub?
它几乎都浮不起来了
It barely floats.
-你知道？
You know it?
-我当然知道
Yeah, I know it.
那是我的船  那是购买酒吧时附带的
It's mine. It came with the bar.
虽然我很欢迎你入住那里
Listen, you are more than welcome to stay there...
但我强烈建议你戴上呼吸管睡觉
but I highly advise you sleep with a snorkel.
-好的  -还有
- Okay. - Also...
小心鳄鱼
watch out for the crocodile.
-小心什么？  -我可没骗你
- The what? - I shit you not,
-去年尚茜就惨遭毒手？
it killed Shantsie last year.
-谁
Who?
码头管理员的博美犬
The dock master's Pomeranian.
顺便提醒一句…
Oh, um... and heads up...
船的名字也是我叔叔起的
My uncle named the boat, too.
小船
你就是那个被弗兰基  卷入水深火热之中的可怜人？
You're the poor soul Frankie's got bunkin' on this frying pan?
对  正是我
Uh, yeah, I am.
好吧
Yeah, well...
你最好小心那只该死的鳄鱼
you best watch out for that damn croc.
欢迎来到无可争议的
Welcome to the undisputed
终极格斗冠军赛
UFC middleweight
世界中量级冠军赛现场！
championship of the world!
首先有请挑战者登场
Introducing first, the challenger...
埃尔伍德道尔顿！
Elwood Dalton!
嘿  道尔顿  道尔顿
Dalton. Dalton!
门上没有门铃
There's no doorbell.
可能是因为这是一艘船
Probably 'cause it's a boat.
我先把衣服穿上
I should put something on.
不必在意这些
Don't worry about it.
我家中有兄弟  习惯了
I got brothers.
想到你应该还没吃早餐
I figured you wouldn't have a chance to get breakfast, so...
我就带了一些食物过来
I brought some food.
你把这里布置得真不错
Love what you've done with the place.
需要我帮忙整理行李吗？
Help you unpack?
不用了  我就这一箱行李
Uh, no, I just have this suitcase.
好吧
Okay.
我看看  我给你带了脆玉米饼…
Let's see, we got tostadas.
早餐卷饼
Breakfast burrito.
还有馅饼
And empanadas.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Ah. Thank you, ma'am. - Yeah.
听着
Uh, look. So um...
我们已经见过不少你这样的保镖
We've been through a lot of you guys.
先是亚瑟  然后是贝内特
You know, there's Arthur. And then, Bennett, and...
还有一个叫克里斯的家伙
this guy, Chris, who, like, I thought...
我原以为他或许能撑一段时间
might last a little while...
但…  他是前海军陆战队员  虎背熊腰
but he's ex-Marine, just, huge guy.
但脑子不太好使
But, um, total idiot.
只坚持了不到两天
Lasted less than two days.
在那之后  我原本打算辞职的  但…
I was gonna leave after that...
现在你来了
but now you're here.
希望你会有所不同
I'm hoping you're different.
情况也许会有所好转
Maybe it'll get better.
谢谢你的食物
Thank you for the food.
早上好  道尔顿
Good morning, Dalton.
早
Morning.
嘿  道尔顿
Hey, Dalton.
你好吗？
How you doin'?
嗨  查莉
Hiya, Charlie.
嘿
Hey.
有什么能帮到你  哥们？
Um, what can I do for you, partner?
我想知道你们这附近有没有电脑  可供我借用一下
Kinda wondering if maybe you had a computer around these parts I could use.
就在那边
Mmm-hmm! Over there.
不瞒你说  我刚才还有点担心  你是来归还《大树弗雷德》的
Not gonna lie, I was kinda worried you came here to return Fred the Tree.
我为什么要这么做？
Why would I do that?
那样我上哪了解群岛著名的六趾猫？
How else am I supposed to learn about the Keys' famous six-toed cats?
有道理
Good point.
我有个好消息
And I have some good news.
我找到了你的生平故事
I found your life story.
这未必算好消息  不过…
I don't know if that's good news.
马丁霍利写的《命丧双叉》
Death at the Double X by Martin Holly.
20世纪50年代的西部故事平装书
Paperback western from the 1950s.
原来如此  西部故事
- Oh, right. A western. - Mmm-hmm.
“勇猛的韦德韦科从未遇到过
"The intrepid Wade Waco never met a scoundrel...
他无法绳之以法的恶棍
"he couldn't bring to justice.
“但话又说回来
"But then again..."
韦德此前从未踏足过双叉
"Wade had never stepped foot in the Double X..."
“一间偷盗、诈骗
"A saloon, red-hot with rustlin',"
抢劫和谋杀案频发的酒馆”
"cheatin', robbin', and murder."
你应该很勇猛吧？
You're intrepid, right?
说实话  我也说不准
Honestly, I couldn't tell ya.
密码是四个零
It's four zeros.
好的
Okay.
能打开吗？
Yeah. That work?
打开了
Yeah.
-把东西还回来！  -你他妈的闭嘴！
- Bring those back! - Shut the fuck up!
妈的！我受够了！
God damn it! I'm sick of this!
-闭上你的臭嘴！
Shut your ass up.
-要么还回来  要么付钱！滚回店里吧！
- Bring those back or pay for them! - Get back in there!
-还想再来吗？  -你要怎么做？
Whatcha gonna do, huh?
滚回店里吧
Go back in there!
鸡鸡歪歪的软蛋-
Big talk. What a fuckin' loser.
-嘿！  -干吗？
Hey!
都给我滚远点！
Get out of here, all of you!
为何不回家问你爸去？-
Why don't you go find your daddy?
快点
Now!
好-
Yeah, okay.
走啊
Go on.
快走
Go!
见鬼
Oh, shit.
-好吧  我看见他了
All right. Let's see it.
-去你的
Fuck you.
你拿着根球棒做什么？
What're you doing with that bat?
我讨厌那些混蛋
I hate those a-holes.
你爸爸呢？
Where's your dad?
他去干另一份活了
He's just at his other job.
光靠卖书为生有点困难
It's kinda hard to make a living on selling books.
确实
Yeah.
开这家书店其实是我妈妈的主意
The bookstore was actually my mom's idea.
她人呢？
And where's she?
她去年走了
She died last year.
我深表遗憾
I'm sorry to hear that.
世事无常嘛
Shit happens.
只不过在这里  糟糕的事情总发生在美好的日子
Only here, it always happens on a beautiful day.
你明天有事吗？-
Hey, you working tomorrow?
-你看这样行吗？  -没问题  包在我身上
- Yeah, no, it sounds good. - Make it work?
我知道的-
Yeah, no, I got you.
下周四你能帮我吗？-
Hey, can you cover me next Thursday?
下周四 这个…-
Thursday, that's...
嘿  他来了
Hey, there he is.
在海上度过的第一个晚上怎么样？
How was your first night at sea?
我还挺喜欢的
I think I liked it.
不过我做了一些奇怪的梦
Yeah, but I did have some strange dreams.
船梦
Boat dreams.
海浪摇晃造成的
It's the rockin' of the ocean.
那些梦会把你的睡眠习惯  搅得一团糟  真的
It'll mess all your sleep patterns and shit up, I swear to God.
-很有趣  对吧？  -对
- It's fun, right? - Yeah.
回头见  弗兰基
See you, Frankie.
-嘿  道尔顿
Hey, Dalton.
-回头见  卡尔
Smell you later, Carl.
-弗兰基  -怎么了？
- Uh, Frankie? - Yeah?
你们开了镇民大会吗？
Was there, like, a town meeting or something?
怎么大家都知道我的名字？这个嘛
- How does everybody know my name? - Yeah, uh...
这里的民风就是这样  人人都爱八卦
that's just how it is around here, man. I mean, it's a gossipy sort of island.
本先生  抱歉我们来晚了
Mr. B. Sorry, we're late.
对  没关系  你们来了就好
Yeah, not at all. Glad you're here.
因为你们在这里  那就说明你们没在别的地方搞砸事情
Because if you're here, that means you're not somewhere else fucking shit up.
你  过来刮完它  我胡子刚刮到一半
You, let's finish this. I got half a fucking shave.
本先生  也许您应该  等到上岸后再刮胡子
Mr. B, maybe you should hold off on that shave till we get to shore.
-风浪挺大的  -别紧张
- It's pretty rough. - Relax.
船长向我保证会平稳航行的  对吧？
Captain assured me it's gonna be smooth sailing, right?
-平稳航行？  -是  老板！
- Smooth sailing? - Yes, boss!
平稳航行
Smooth sailing.
再说了  这关你什么事？
Also, what the fuck do you care?
对
Right.
话说回来  不知道您都听到了什么
Anyway, I don't know what you heard.
我听到的是  你们都是一群该死的懦夫
What I heard is that you're all a bunch of fucking pussies.
大家都这么说的-
That's what I heard.
害怕某个混帐保镖  这就是我听到的
Scared of some bouncer asshole. That's what I heard.
本先生  那其实是戴尔的错
Actually, sir, it was Dell.
是他不确定该怎么处理
He wasn't sure how to handle it.
好吧  那就让这位天才戴尔  过来跟我说两句
Okay, let me talk to this genius, Dell, then.
不行
You can't.
这又是为什么？
And why is that?
他现在还躺在医院里
He's still in the hospital.
有点脑震荡
He's got a concussion.
王八蛋！
Son of a bitch!
-对不起
I'm sorry.
-没事  好的
It's fine. It's fine. Okay. Okay.
保持手腕放松  好吗？
Let's keep the wrist nice and loose, okay?
-能做到吧？好极了  -好的
- Sounds good? Perfect. - Okay.
继续
You can go ahead.
谁能告诉我或提醒我一下
Can someone just tell me or remind me
当初是谁提议雇用这群笨蛋的吗？
whose idea was it to hire these dumb fucks in the first place?
是你  老板  最重要的是！
- Yours, boss. - Here's the fucking thing!
你们早就该办好这件事了
You're all supposed to have this job done by now.
我还是觉得我们可以吓跑他们
I still think we could scare 'em off.
你是不是…我刚才怎么说的？
Are you, I... What did I say?
我说保持放松  懂吗？放松双手
I said keep it loose, okay? Hands loose.
我知道船身有点颠簸  但放松点
I get it. It's a little bouncy, but keep it nice and loose.
你只要放松点就好  好吗？很简单
That's all you have to do, okay? Easy.
好吗？
Okay?
你  跟我说说这个保镖的情况
You, tell me about this bouncer.
这个…
Oh, uh...
我也不太清楚  他…
Yeah, uh, I don't know, man. He's um...
他这个人挺奇怪的
He's kinda strange, you know?
“奇怪”是什么意思？
What do you mean, strange?
怎么说呢  你懂的  他…
Yeah. I mean, you know, he's...
他看起来就像儿童节目主持人  一副人畜无害的样子
He acts all nice and shit, like he's Mister Rogers or something.
但转眼间  他却突然暴走
But then, man, he hauls off, he hauls off.
把你揍得屁滚尿流
He beats the living shit outta you.
总的来说  是个非常有趣的家伙
So, really interesting guy overall.
真是精彩的分析
That was a brilliant analysis.
山姆  把这些笨蛋扔到海里
Sam, throw these dum-dums overboard.
也许您告诉我们拆除路边餐馆的原因  我们会好办些？
Well, maybe if you just told us why you want to tear down the Road House?
好主意！
Great idea!
干脆把我的全盘生意都告诉你们好了
Let me bring you in on all my business dealings.
通通给我滚
Get the fuck outta here.
滚到别墅去  尽情享受吧
Go to the house. Enjoy your fucking selves.
我回头再找你们
I'll be in touch.
也许该请你老爸出手了
Well, maybe it's time we get your old man involved.
船长！我有话跟你说
Captain! Let me talk to you for a second.
现场乐队  周四到周日
我知道这里是酒吧
Hey, everybody. I know we're at a bar right now,
但你们不介意  我把教堂“搬”到这里吧？
but do y'all mind if I take y'all to church?
♪ 感谢上帝赐予我们南方女人  悍米引擎  脆皮鸡 ♪
♪ Praise the Lord for southern women Hemi engines, crispy chicken ♪
♪ 感谢上帝赐予我们东亚特兰大… ♪
♪ Praise the Lord for East Atlanta ♪ - Yo.
这是什么鬼音乐？
Yo, what the fuck kinda music is this?
♪ 感谢上帝赐予我一切- ♪
♪ Praise the Lord that I got everything ♪
能不能唱点人听的歌
Yo, play some fucking Stones or something.
滚下去…给我滚下舞台
Get off the fucking stage!
这可不是高中生的车库乐队  表演的地方！
Yo! This ain't fuckin' high school garage band!
给我滚下舞台！
Get off the fuckin' stage!
你有什么毛病  兄弟？
The fuck is wrong with you, bro?
坐下吧  该死的醉汉
Sit the fuck down, you drunk motherfucker.
你打算怎么做？少管闲事！
The fuck you're gonna do about it? Mind your fuckin' business!
♪ 感谢上帝- ♪
♪ Praise the Lord ♪
这该死的音乐烂透了
This fuckin' music sucks!
那个穿红衣服的家伙  衬衫下藏着一把刀
That guy's got a knife under his shirt. The one in red.
老子不怕你
I ain't fuckin' scared of you, motherfucker.
-给我坐回去  -不
- Sit the fuck down. - Sit your ass down.
-你来处理吧？
Do you wanna handle it?
-不  你才给我坐下
No, just sit your ass down.
我？
Me?
老子不怕你
I ain't fuckin' scared of you.
-你他妈的给我退下  -滚出去
- Back the fuck up. - Get the fuck out.
从我面前滚开  贱货！
Back the fuck up outta of my face, bitch!
当他掏出刀的时候
When he takes it out,
你只须后撤一大步  然后一拳打在他脸上
you just take a big step back and pop him in the face.
你可以的
You can do it.
好的  好的
Okay. Okay.
♪ 海米引擎，脆皮鸡- ♪
♪ Hemi engines, crispy chicken ♪
♪ 跟我说“嘿”- ♪
♪ I said, "Hey!" ♪
嘿！
Hey! All right, hey!
给我滚出去  伙计  滚出去
- You're fucking out, man. - Get the fuck off!
给我滚出去  伙计
You're fuckin' out, man.
你少管闲事！
Stay the fuck outta this!
这下如何  贱人？怎么了？
What now, bitch? What's up?
♪ 一起摇摆- ♪
♪ He rockin' with me ♪
♪ 绝对真心- ♪
♪ That's for sure ♪
♪ 感谢上帝…- ♪
♪ Praise the Lord ♪
王八蛋！
Motherfucker!
该死的！
Ahh! Fuck!
比利  椅子
Billy, chair.
♪ 感谢上帝…- ♪
♪ Praise the Lord, praise the Lord ♪
♪ 一起摇摆- ♪
♪ He rockin' with me ♪
你藏着一把刀进来  这可是禁忌
You brought a concealed knife in here and that is a no-no.
-比利  -见鬼  老兄！我的胳膊！
- Billy. - Ow! Fuck, man! My arm!
交给你了
You got him.
冷静点  老兄  冷静点
Chill. Chill, dude, chill.
你才冷静点  别再做这种事了
You fucking chill. Don't fucking ever do that again.
♪ 感谢上帝…- ♪
♪ Praise the Lord, praise the Lord ♪
放开我
Get off of me.
滚出去  伙计！
Get the fuck outta here, man.
给我滚出去
Get the fuck outta here.
搞什么  伙计？
- Jesus, what the fuck, man? - Get out.
-看我不打死你！  -去你的
- I will fuck you up! - Oh, fuck!
我越来越得心应手了
You know, I think I'm getting pretty good at this.
你有这方面的天赋  别忘了要靠膝盖发力
You're a natural. Don't forget to lift with your knees.
靠膝盖发力
Lift with my knees.
台球桌那边  穿绿衣服的家伙
Pool table. Guy in green.
嘿  退下  给我退下
Hey, back up. Back the fuck up.
他能充当保镖真是太好了
It's a good thing he can do that.
因为他是个糟糕的酒保
'Cause, you know, he's a pretty crap bartender.
屌-
It's cool.
大家都冷静点
Everyone relax.
别冲动
Don't fucking do that.
嘿  你是瑞夫  对吧？我是
- Hey, you're Reef, right? - Yeah.
你那天毫不犹豫就出手帮了比利
You were quick to back Billy up the other day.
对  我讨厌恶霸  所以…
Yeah, I mean, I don't like bullies, so...
你指关节上那些是疤痕吗？
Those scars on your knuckles there?
老习惯了  我在大学期间打过拳
Old habit. Used to box some in college.
现在还练吗？
Still hit the bag?
偶尔会练一下  为何这么问？
Every now and then. Why?
♪ 昨晚  我喝醉了 ♪
♪ Last night ♪
♪ -放开我  -好痛  伙计！
- Get the fuck off me! ♪ I got loaded ♪
♪ 喝了一瓶杜松子酒 ♪
♪ On a bottle'a gin ♪
♪ 昨晚 ♪
♪ Last night ♪
♪ 我喝醉了 ♪
♪ I got loaded ♪
♪ 喝了一瓶杜松子酒 ♪
♪ On a bottle'a gin ♪
嘿  女士们  从桌子上下来
Yo, ladies, get off the table.
♪ 那感觉棒极了 ♪
♪ Well, I feel all right ♪
♪ 感觉棒极了 ♪
♪ I feel all right ♪
♪ 感觉棒极了  那感觉棒极了 ♪
♪ I feel all right You know I feel all right ♪
嘿  伙计
Hey, man!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
♪ 喝了一瓶威士忌 ♪
♪ On a bottle'a whiskey ♪
起来！
Get up!
♪ 昨晚 ♪
♪ Last night ♪
♪ 我喝醉了  喝了一瓶威士忌 ♪
♪ I got loaded on a bottle'a whiskey ♪
喝了一瓶威士忌
Back the fuck up, man! Hey!
退后-
Back away!
♪ 但我感觉棒极了  感觉棒极了 ♪
♪ But I feel all right You know I feel all right ♪
♪ 感觉棒极了 ♪
♪ I feel all right ♪
朱利叶斯！
Julius!
你说得对  这么做感觉很爽
Hey, you was right. That was mad therapeutic.
对  不过记得要靠膝盖发力
Yeah, but remember, lift with your knees.
-好的  -始终抬起膝盖
- Always lift with your knees. - Sure.
有人吗？
Hello?
嘿！临走前我想再喝一杯
Hey! One for the road.
我看你已经醉得不能上路了
Yeah, I think even the road is drunk at this point.
-什么？  -我帮你打辆车
- What? - I'll call you a cab.
-不要  -要
- No, no. Boo! - Yeah.
切
Boo!
嘿！不行  休想！
Hey! No.
就一瓶
- Fuck, no! - Just one. One!
怎么了？
What?
又是你
Hey, there, again.
“又”？
"Again"?
不
Uh... Nope.
我们从未见过面
We've, um, never met.
好了  小心台阶
All right. Watch your step.
明早记得过来拿这个  吉姆
Pick these up in the morning, Jim.
回头见  道尔顿
Later, Dalton.
我们会回来的-
We'll be back.
第一位称重的拳手
First fighter to the scale.
挑战者  埃尔伍德道尔顿！
The challenger, Elwood Dalton!
天啊  这混蛋看得我只想笑  因为他就是个笑话！
Man, this guy makes me laugh, 'cause he's a fucking joke!
-去你的！  -轻轻一巴掌而已
- You fuck! - Just a little slap.
你死定了
You're fucking dead.
- You're fucking dead. - Wow.
该死的船梦
Fucking boat dreams.
佛罗里达群岛本地历史  大树弗雷德
谢谢
Thank you.
你在这里
You're here.
是的  我看到书上说  这是群岛最棒的海“挪”杂绘
I am. Best conch chowder in the Keys, so I've read.
海螺
Conch.
抱歉  什么？
Sorry, what?
是“海螺”  不是“海挪”
It's conch, not con-ch.
发型不错嘛  艾莉  很适合你
Nice haircut, Ellie. Really suits you.
去你的  弗兰克
Oh, fuck you, Frank.
早知道我当初就该  任由你死于阑尾破裂
I should've let that burst appendix kill you.
他是我的理发师
My hairdresser.
我现在自己剪头发了
I cut my own hair now.
这里的人似乎有点好勇斗狠
People seem a little aggressive around here.
我必须提醒你
Look, I should warn you.
我从小在玻璃岛长大
I grew up in Glass Key
这里的人有自己的一套处事方式
and people have a certain way of getting things done around here.
忠诚和家族的观念根深蒂固
Loyalties, family ties run deep.
即便是警察  有时候也会无法提供应有的帮助
Even the cops aren't always as helpful as they should be.
一旦惹错了人  很有可能会受伤  甚至更糟
If you cause trouble to the wrong people, you could get hurt or worse.
我那本《大树弗雷德》  完全没有提到这些
None of this is covered in my Fred the Tree book.
你确定？
You sure?
你把整本书都看完了？
You read the whole thing?
你知道海螺能产珍珠吗？
You know that conchs produce pearls?
知道
Yes.
-它们有着华丽的螺旋状…
And that they have ornate spiral...
-贝壳？对  这点无人不知
Shells. Yes, everyone knows that.
而且每15000个海螺  才有一个能产出粉红色的珍珠
That one in every 15,000 produces a pink pearl.
听起来很浪漫
Sounds romantic.
但对海螺来说则不然
Unless you're a conch.
因为珍珠的形成实际上是
Because what actually happens
海螺的贝壳里进了沙粒
is the conch gets a bit of grit inside its shell,
给它造成了极大的痛苦
which causes extreme irritation.
在“极大的痛苦”中
"Extreme irritation"...
孕育出美丽的事物
that leads to something beautiful.
这怎么就不浪漫了？
How is that not romantic?
好好享用你的海螺杂烩吧
Enjoy your conch chowder.
我喜欢你的发型  你剪得很好
I like your hair. Did a nice job.
去他的弗兰克
Fuck Frank.
♪ 哟  人生何其短  珍惜眼前人 ♪
♪ Yo, well, life is too short So love the one you got ♪
♪ 皆因生命太无常  车祸中枪无定数 ♪
♪ 'Cause you might get run over Or you might get shot ♪
♪ 从不与人口角  只求一吐为快 ♪
♪ Never start no static I just get it off my chest ♪
♪ 防弹背心从未派上用场 ♪
♪ Never had to battle With no bullet-proof vest ♪
♪ 举个小小的例子  请君听我一句劝 ♪
♪ Take a small example Take a tip from me ♪
♪ 将所有钱财拿去做善事 ♪
♪ Take all your money And give it to charity ♪
♪ 爱是我所拥有的  它触手可及 ♪
♪ Love is what I got It's within my reach ♪
♪ 轻松愉快的风格源自新奥尔良 ♪
♪ And the jelly style Is straight from New Orleans ♪
♪ 种什么因  得什么果  善恶到头终有报 ♪
♪ It all comes back to you You're bound to get what you deserve ♪
♪ 不信来试试  必将尝苦果 ♪
♪ Try and test that You're bound to get served ♪
♪ 爱是我所拥有的  切忌纵情欢闹 ♪
♪ Love is what I got, don't start a riot ♪
♪ 舞会进入高潮  便能体会得到 ♪
♪ You'll feel it when the dance gets hot ♪
那是我叔叔
That's my uncle.
开玩笑而已  那才是我叔叔
Just kidding. That's my uncle.
-那位幽默的仁兄？
Funny one, huh?
-对  我以前也理解不了他
Yeah. I mean, I didn't get the dude.
但不知为何  随着年岁增长
I don't know. But now that I'm older,
我想我现在更欣赏他了
I think I'm startin' to appreciate him more.
他当年可是个强悍的家伙
I mean, he was a tough bastard.
知道吗？-
You know?
要做到他所做的事  必须得强悍
He had to be to do what he did.
在60年代的南方
Build this place...
经营起这样一家餐馆
in the '60s in the South?
那家伙可是下了苦功夫的
That dude didn't fuck around.
我不想辜负他的努力
I wanna be worthy of that.
嘿  需要载你一程吗？
Hey, want a ride?
不用了  劳拉  祝你晚安
No. You have a good night, Laura.
我走路就好
- I'm gonna walk. - Okay.
该死的  戴尔！
Damn it, Dell!
-闭嘴  你给我闭嘴！  -我的卡车！
- Shut up. Just shut up! - My fucking truck!
快  快从卡车上下来
Come on, get the fuck off this truck!
真糟糕！我开不动这玩意  快跑！
It sucks! I can't drive this shit. Move!
不！
No, no!
我不在乎什么卡车  重要的是我们干掉他了
Forget about the truck. We got him!
你就是个鸟人-
You're really an asshole.
没有的事-
Yeah, I haven't heard that one before.
离开这鬼地方吧-
Come on, let's get the fuck out of here.
你可真让我头疼
You're a real pain in my ass.
好吧
Okay.
我原本还希望让今晚的事  看起来像一场意外
I was hoping tonight would look more like an accident.
醉酒司机肇事  那样问题会少一些
Drunk driver. Less questions that way.
但是…
But...
我还是直接打死你算了
I'mma just shoot you.
我能问你一个问题吗？
Can I ask you a question?
为何如此兴师动众？
Why all the fuss?
我只是个无名小卒罢了
I mean, I'm just some guy.
才不是为了你  是那家路边餐馆！
Oh, hell, it ain't you. It's the Road House!
放弃挣扎吧
Come on, man!
该死的！
Fuck! Help.
可恶！
Fuck!
-你现在要杀了我吗？
So, you're gonna kill me now?
-我为什么要杀你？
Why would I kill you?
真是有够愚蠢的  我现在就上来…
Well, that was stupid. I'm just gonna go right back up.
妈呀！
Oh, shit!
-真见鬼！
Help me! Fuck!
-抓紧
Hang on! Hang on.
抓紧！我拉住你了  我拉住你了
Hang on, I got you! I got you. I got you!
-去你的！  -抓紧
- Fuck you! - Hold on. Hold on.
门罗县警长
他们找不到尸体的
Won't find the body.
鳄鱼喜欢把食物藏起来
Crocs hide their food.
我还真不知道
I didn't know that.
所以我当初说了  也没人相信尚茜的事
That's why no one believed me about Shantsie.
我的狗
My dog.
也被那该死的鳄鱼吃了
Damn croc got him, too.
话说那个混蛋为什么要找你麻烦？
Hey. What'd that asshole want with you anyways?
想必是你妨碍到他做生意了
Must've got in the way of his business.
是吗？什么生意？
Oh, yeah? What's his business?
我也不知道
Hell, I don't know.
估计是毒品
Drugs, probably.
这里到处都是那玩意
I mean, that's all we got around here.
不然怎么会得名“毒岛”呢？
Why do you think they call it the Keys?
船会把货物  送到路边餐馆背后  然后…
Deliveries by boat to the back of the Road House. And...
-不  这是…  -可以放大一点吗？
- No, it's... You're... No. - Can you... zoom?
不…
No, you...
-我不知道怎么操作  -你想放大吗？
- I don't know how these things work. - No. You wanna zoom in?
好了  放大了
Okay, there. Zoomed.
不过这里才是玻璃岛
But Glass Key's here.
好的  等一下
Okay, just wait.
这里是路边餐馆后面的露台  对吧？
That's... Right there is the back deck, right? Of the Road House?
所以如果我想走水路运送货物…
So, if you wanted to get deliveries by boat...
那你就倒霉了
Then you'd be plumb out of luck.
为什么？
Why?
因为礁石
Because of the reefs.
路边餐馆这片水域的水深不够
You see, this area by the Road House, it's just not deep enough.
船驶进去就会搁浅
Boats would run aground.
也就是说餐馆无法接收水运货物
All right. So, you can't get deliveries and...
而且还靠近高速公路  毫无私密性可言
it's close to the highway, so there's no privacy.
这听起来越来越像西部悬疑片
This is kind of sounding more like a mystery-western...
而不是典型的西部枪战片了
instead of a straight-up shooting-western. Know what I mean?
对  确实如此
Yeah, it kinda is.
嘿！
Hey!
那家书店挺不错的吧？
Is that a good bookstore?
挺不错的  我喜欢
Yeah, I like it.
看起来你和那女孩  在里面相处得挺愉快的
Yeah. Sure looked like you and that girl were having a grand time in there.
嘿
Hey.
嘿！
Hey!
上车吧  老板有话跟你说
Get in the car. Boss wants to have a word with you.
-你老板是谁？
Who's your boss?
-布兰特
Brandt.
布兰特？
Brandt?
对  本布兰特
Yeah, Ben Brandt.
他正等着  你到底上不上车？
And he's waiting. So, you're gonna get in the car or not?
-恕不奉陪  -站住  你给我站住！
- I don't think so. - Hey, stop. Stop!
你应该看到我有枪了吧？
You did see that I have a fucking gun, right?
当然看到了  你都特意露给我看了
Yeah. You made a pretty big point of showin' it to me.
行吧  那就上车吧
Okay, so get in the fucking car!
你还不明白这是怎么回事  对吧？
You don't understand how this works, do you?
我明白
Yeah, I do.
但你把枪塞在腰带里
But you have a gun, tucked in your waistband.
真的没什么威慑力
So, it's really not that intimidating, is it?
你在胡说什么？
What the fuck are you talkin' about?
我只要掰断你的食指和中指
I mean, all I have to do is break your index and your middle finger
你便无法握住那把枪
and you wouldn't be able to hold that gun.
准确来说是无法开枪
Technically, you'd be able to hold it but you wouldn't be able to fire it.
所以这并不是什么重大威胁
So it's really not that big of a threat, is it?
不跟你啰嗦了
Fuck this.
王八蛋！
Motherfucker!
去你的！
Fuck you!
你个混蛋  王八蛋！
You cocksucker, motherfucker!
你弄断了我的手指！
You broke my fucking finger!
现在懂我的意思了吧？这可痛了
You see what I mean? It's really painful.
你应该不是钢琴家之类的吧？
You're not like a piano player or anything, are you?
-去你的
Fuck you.
-你不会也带了枪吧？
You don't have a gun, too, do you?
我的枪好像落在车里了
I think I left it in the car.
告诉你们老板  如果他想找我谈话
Tell your boss, if he wants to talk to me,
我就在路边餐馆工作  每晚都在那里
I work at the Road House, and I'm there every night.
-该死的！  -好的
- Damn it! - Okay.
对了  你的朋友需要立刻就医
And your friend is gonna need a doctor now.
不过好消息是  25分钟车程外就有一家医院
But the good news is, there is a hospital. It's only 25 minutes away.
-嗨  伙计们  -嘿  弗兰基
- Hi, guys. - Hey, Frankie.
天啊  你吓死我了
Holy shit. You scared the shit out of me.
我正有此意
That was kind of my intention.
我听说戴尔的事了
I heard about Dell.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
我没事
I... Yeah, I'm fine.
听着  戴尔就是个人渣
Listen, Dell was a piece of shit.
好吗？他和他那群狐朋狗友  恐吓了我们好几个月
Okay? He and his friends terrorized us for months.
对于他的死  我知道我们不该幸灾乐祸
And I know we shouldn't be happy that he's dead
而我却在暗自高兴  这非常不对
and the fact that I am happy is a huge problem.
我得好好纠正这种心态
And it's something I'm gonna work on.
但是…
But...
要我怎么说呢
I don't know.
我实在想不明白  他为何对路边餐馆如此执着
I just don't get why he was so focused on the Road House.
此话怎讲？
What do you mean?
你刚才也说了  他恐吓你们已有数月之久
I mean, you just said he terrorized this place for months.
我也不知道
Shit, man. I don't know.
这些家伙有的领地意识特别强
I mean, some of these guys, they get real territorial.
天知道这些混蛋的动机是什么
Who knows why these assholes do what they do?
但我是你的话  就不会想那么多
But if I were you, I wouldn't read too much into it.
所以说  你认为问题不大？
So, you think it's nothing?
这么说吧  我希望你没有因此而失眠
Put it this way. I hope you didn't lose any sleep over it.
我确实失眠了
Well, I did.
一点点
Uh, a little.
你的手指怎么了？
What happened to your fingers?
被那个保镖掰断了
He broke them. The bouncer.
他掰断了你的手指？
He broke your fingers?
对  他还抢走了我的枪
Yeah, when he took my gun.
好吧
Okay.
你可真行
That's great. Great work.
至少你没有葬身鳄鱼之口
At least you didn't get eaten by a crocodile.
你觉得这很有趣吗？
You find that funny?
你觉得这很好笑吗？我可笑不出来
You find this fucking amusing? I'm not amused.
放下那玩意  很贵的
Put that fucking down! It's expensive.
这个该死的保镖
This fuckin' bouncer...
正在妨碍我实现我的梦想
is standing in the way of my fuckin' dreams.
我都快被他气死了
He's fucking killin' me.
我努力构建的一切
And you're here laughing
正付诸东流  你却在那哈哈大笑
as everything I've been trying to build is going down the drain.
爸爸
您好  这是一通预付电话…
Hello. This is a prepaid call from...
回复“是”吧  白痴
Say yes, shithead.
呼叫方为…佛罗里达惩教所的囚犯
An inmate at Florida Correctional Institution.
本次通话将被录音和监控
This call is subject to recording and monitoring.
若接受收费  请回复“是”
To accept charges, say yes.
把我的手机捞上来
Go get my phone.
再见！吾爱-
- My love! - Goodbye!
您好  这是一通预付电话  呼叫方为…
Hello. This is a prepaid call from
-佛罗里达惩教所…
an inmate at Florida Correctional...
-是  诺克斯  我是杰拉尔德布兰特
- Yes. Knox? It's Gerald Brandt.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
我在挑衣服
Clothes shopping.
你问这个干吗？
What the fuck do you care?
我在佛罗里达遇到了一个大麻烦
I got a serious fucking problem in Florida.
等一下
Hang on.
诺克斯！喂！-
Knox! Hello? Knox!
说吧  找我有什么事？
- So, what do you need? Knox...
-我那儿子成事不足  败事有余  -好的
- my idiot son is fucking things up. - Yes?
-我需要你的帮忙  -好的
- Yeah. I need your help.
我马上出发
I'll leave right away.
嘿
Ahoy.
好漂亮的船
Nice boat.
我前男友的
Ex-boyfriend's.
但我知道他的备用钥匙藏在哪儿
But I know where he hides the spare key.
开玩笑而已  这是他借我用的
I'm kidding. He lets me use it.
他是一名警察
He's a cop.
敢跟我来吗？
Feeling brave?
我们这是去哪儿？
Where are we going?
到了
We're here.
在海中央？
In the middle of the ocean?
你若需要…
Uh, you need any, uh...
来吧
Come on.
等一下…
Wait, why are...
来吧  拿上冷藏箱
Come on, grab the cooler.
好吧
All right.
他们找不到那家伙的尸体的
They're not gonna find that guy's body.
鳄鱼喜欢把食物藏起来
Crocs hide their food.
这里的幼儿园都在教这个吗？
Do they teach that in kindergarten around here?
确实
They do.
所以我之前才警告你
This is why I warned you.
显然你踩到某人的尾巴了
You obviously stepped on someone's toes.
一个叫布兰特的人
Some guy named Brandt.
谁告诉你的？
Who told you that?
为何这么问？
Why?
你认识他？
Do you know him?
他家是佛罗里达州的老牌家族之一
He comes from one of those old Florida families.
大半个玻璃岛都是他们建造的
They built most of Glass Key.
话说  你是哪里人？
So, where are you from?
我？
Me?
蒙大拿州
Montana.
蒙大拿州哪里？
Where in Montana?
米苏拉市
Missoula.
-那是个好地方吗？
Is it a nice place?
-我想我们也许该回去了
Look, I think maybe we should head back.
我们才刚到
We just got here.
回去吧
Let's head back.
我只是问了一些简单的问题
I was just asking simple questions.
我之前没考虑清楚  没有意识到这是约会
I just didn't think this through. I didn't realize this was a date.
你这人怎么回事？
What's wrong with you?
你是…你是一个好人
You're a nice person.
你不会想认识我的
You don't wanna know me.
我想做什么  不用你来告诉我
Don't tell me what I want.
你以为我们这里没有互联网吗？
You think we don't have the Internet out here?
我知道发生了什么
I know what happened.
而你也知道这是约会
And you know this is a date.
哪个王八蛋的摩托车  竟敢拦本大爷的路？
Who put those fuckin' bikes in me way?
你又是哪来的王八蛋？
Who the fuck are you?
感谢上帝
Thank you, God.
三明治
Sandwiches.
我都快饿死了
I'm fucking famished.
天啊  他把所有摩托车都撞倒了
Jesus. He knocked all the fuckin' bikes over.
你惹上大麻烦了  兔崽子
Now you got a big-ass problem, bucko.
可不是吗
No shit.
首先
First off...
三个三明治还远远不够  我需要更多食物
I'm gonna need more than three sandwiches.
我话还没说完呢
I wasn't done talkin'.
事实上  你这么想就错了  小子
Actually, that's where you're wrong, lad.
开什么国际玩笑
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
靠边停下
Pull up.
你他妈的开什么玩笑？-
Are you fucking kidding me?
你这是在干什么？
What the fuck are you doing?
嘿  布兰特先生  我只是想搭个吊床
Hey, Mr. Brandt. Just putting up a hammock.
这是我父亲的别墅  不是该死的民宿
It's my father's house. It's not a goddamn Airbnb.
-可分明是您让我们尽情享受的
Right, but you told us to enjoy ourselves.
-不  我没有  -您在船上说过的
- No, I didn't. - You did. On the boat.
-就算我说了  也不是认真的
And if I fucking did, I didn't mean it.
好吧
Okay.
你那些白痴朋友去哪了？
Where are your idiot friends?
他们去准备食物了
They went to make some food.
以防您肚子饿
In case you're hungry.
把这烂摊子收拾干净！  这些人又是谁？
Clean this shit up! Who are these people?
滚出去！
Get out of here!
不好意思  你是谁啊？
I'm sorry, who the fuck are you?
嘿
Hey.
我给你带来个口信
I got a message for you.
是你父亲给你的
From your father.
口信？我父亲？
A message? My father? And what...
什么“口信”？
What is this "message"?
你是本  对吧？杰瑞的儿子？
You're Ben, right? Jerry's son?
这是我存放东西的地方
This is where I'll store my stuff.
楼上那间主卧现在是我的了
And that master bedroom up there is mine.
你在胡说什么？
What are you talking about?
你谁啊？
Who are you?
你老爸说你成事不足  败事有余
Your da says you've been fucking things up.
让我来助你一臂之力
He asked me to lend a hand.
我父亲怎么会知道？
How would my father know?
他正在监狱的牢房里熬着呢
He's in a prison, rotting in a cell.
别傻了  你父亲的眼线无处不在
Don't be silly. Your father has spies everywhere.
那你可以回去告诉我父亲
Well, you can tell my father...
我不需要你帮忙
I don't need your fuckin' help.
一切都在我的掌控之中  并没有
- I have it all under control. - No, you don't.
是真的  我已经派人
Yes, I have people out there right now...
去处理最后一个问题
cleaning up this final issue, and that's all...
-那样就可以…  -随你怎么说
Whatever you say.
-那个混蛋保镖在哪儿？  -好吧
- So, where's this bouncer asshole? - Okay.
能不能先等一下？
Can we just take a minute?
你不能在光天化日之下  当众开枪毙了那个家伙
You can't go and shoot this guy in the middle of town fucking square.
这点你应该明白吧？
You understand that, right?
眼下的情况比较微妙
This is a delicate situation.
如果我们…想要干掉那个家伙  我们就必须…
So, if we're gonna kill this guy...
“如果”？他已经是个死人了
If? He's already dead.
我诺克斯做事  从不失手
Once Knox is on the job, it's over, baby.
只是何时动手的问题
It's just a matter of when.
对  你说得没错  想必如此
Yeah, you're right. I'm sure.
你想必神通广大  无所不能
I'm sure you're amazing. Amazing.
我想再尝试一下简单的解决办法
Um, I'm gonna try to do this the easy way one more time.
-没问题吧？  -你尽管去做
- Is that okay? Yeah. Thank you. - You do your thing. You do your thing.
谢谢  在那之后  你就可以大干一场了  -真是好哥们
- After that, you can set it all on fire. - My man. My man.
-好极了  -对  -上帝保佑
- Wonderful. Yeah. - God bless, God bless.
这家伙是他妈谁…
Who the fuck is...
我们回头见
I'll be seeing you soon.
我知道你住哪里
I know where you live.
道尔顿先生
Mr. Dalton.
什么事？
Yeah?
关于那晚的事  我们有几个问题想问你
We have a few questions about the other night.
需要你跟我们走一趟
Need you to come with us.
好的  有何不可？
Sure. Why not?
就是他吗？
Is that him?
埃尔伍德P道尔顿
Elwood P. Dalton.
埃尔伍德？
Elwood?
大多数人都叫我道尔顿  警官
Most people call me Dalton, sir.
大多数人都叫我大鸡哥
Most people call me Big Dick.
我不会那样叫你的
I'm not gonna do that.
你的名字让我想起了约翰尼卡什的歌
Your name reminds me of that Johnny Cash song.
是吗  哪一首？
Yeah? Which one?
《名为苏的男孩》
"A Boy Named Sue."
男孩的爸爸给他取了个女孩的名字
Dad gave his son a girl's name...
希望他日后能成为一条硬汉
so he'd grow up tough.
你是条硬汉吗  小子？
Are you tough, son?
你的副手说你有些问题想问我
Your deputy says you had some questions for me.
听好了  埃尔伍德
Listen up, Elwood...
我是门罗县的警长
I'm the sheriff of all of Monroe County.
但玻璃岛是个特别的地方  知道为什么吗？
But Glass Key is special. Do you know why?
你把我问倒了  警官
I'm stumped, sir.
我的孩子们是在这里长大的
My children were raised here.
如今生活在这里的人  就像家人一样  明白我的意思吗？
All the people that live here now are like family, you understand?
明白  意思是你热爱玻璃岛？
Yeah. So, you like Glass Key?
我希望你离开这里  我的朋友
I'd like you to leave here, my friend.
你不会想做我的朋友的
You don't want to be my friend.
那样的话
Well, in that case...
有几个办法可以解决这个问题
there are a few ways this can go.
我可以逮捕你
I can arrest you.
理由是什么？
For what?
那不重要  我们会说案卷弄丢了  然后在某一天突然又找到了
Doesn't matter. We'll lose the paperwork. We'll find you someday.
而找到的那天  很可能就是  你被刺死在监狱院子里的日子
Likely, the very same day you get shanked in the yard.
那样的话讽刺感十足
That way, it will be ironic.
会是写歌的好材料
It will make a good song.
如果是一首朗朗上口的歌
Elwood doesn't really rhyme with much, but...
“埃尔伍德”恐怕不太好押韵
I mean, if it's a catchy tune.
把他从车上弄下去！
Get him out of the car!
给我下车！
Get out of the fucking car!
-好的  没问题  -下来！
- All right. All right. All right. - Get out!
你想死吗  小子？
You have a death wish, son?
你这是在干什么？
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
来吧  道尔顿
Come on, Dalton.
他是我的父亲
He's my father.
我母亲去世后  我就离开了群岛
My mom died and I moved away from the Keys...
改名换姓  换成了她的娘家姓
changed my name, took her maiden name.
真不知道我为什么要回来
I don't know why I ever came back.
你之前提到的那个人  本布兰特
The man you talked about, Ben Brandt...
他的父亲是杰拉尔德布兰特
His father is Gerald Brandt.
我爸爸以前曾在他手下做事
My dad used to work for him.
他在玻璃岛投入了大量的金钱
He put a lot of money into Glass Key.
拥有一支包租船队  用于经营旅游业务
Owned a fleet of charter boats that ran tours.
和毒品生意
And drugs.
直到他离开
Until he was gone.
他现在在监狱里
He's in prison now.
我想我父亲现在改为  替他那混账儿子卖命了
And I guess, now my father works for his fucking son.
你必须离开玻璃岛
You have to leave Glass Key.
真是令人唏嘘
It's kinda sad, you know.
想当年这里想必是个美丽的小镇
I bet this was a nice town once.
美丽的小镇倒算不上
Nice towns are overrated.
我们要在这里制造多大的破坏？
And how much damage are we supposed to do here?
必须足够让他知道厉害
Enough to make sure he gets the message.
查莉  从后门出去  快
Charlie, out the back. Quick!
从后门出去！
Out the back!
♪ 我要去市中心  找一家酒吧 ♪
♪ I'm gonna go downtown Gonna find me a bar ♪
♪ 一杯接一杯  直到天明 ♪
♪ Drink and drink till the sun comes up tomorrow ♪
♪ 哦  宝贝 ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ 我要把钱花在自动点唱机上 ♪
♪ I'm gonna spend my money On jukebox songs ♪
♪ 今晚我要尽情起舞  宝贝 ♪
♪ I'm gonna dance the night away, baby ♪
♪ 宝贝 ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ 你直教我惊叹连连 ♪
♪ You got me singin' whoo whoo whoo ♪
♪ 我已不知该如何是好  宝贝 ♪
♪ I don't know what I'm gonna do, baby ♪
♪ 我的宝贝… ♪
♪ My baby ♪
-嘿  发生什么事了？  -嘿
- Hey, what's going on? - Hey.
艾莉打了两通电话过来
Ellie called twice.
让我看到你就给她发短信
Said I needed to text her if you showed up.
你还迟到了
Also, you're late, which...
这还是头一回
is a first.
我和警长之间…
Had a little mix-up...
发生了一点小误会
with the sheriff.
误会？
A mix-up?
什么误会？
What are we talkin' about?
是啊  什么误会？
Yeah, what are we talking about?
我很好奇你会跟她说什么
I'm curious, actually, to hear what you were gonna tell her.
嘿  劳拉
Hey, Laura.
能给我一杯纯伏特加吗？
Can I have a vodka neat, please?
好的
Yeah.
我叫本布兰特
I'm Ben Brandt.
你
You...
你想必就是道尔顿了
you must be Dalton.
让我猜猜  这次轮到你登场  -轮到我？
- Let me guess. It's your turn now. - My turn?
-你懂的  威胁我  让我滚出小镇
You know, to threaten me. Tell me to get out of town.
就像你的朋友大鸡哥那样
Like your buddy, Big Dick.
不  不  我觉得你应该不吃威胁这一套
No. No, I get the impression that you can't be threatened.
我倒是希望威胁有用  但…
I wish you could be, but...
我要是觉得钱有用  花钱收买你也在所不惜
I'd even bribe you, if I thought money would work.
真的吗？多少钱？
Really? How much we talking?
你真会开玩笑
You're funny. You're funny.
我实在忍不住想问  你一个外地人跑到这里来
See, I can't help but wonder what an outsider like you...
到底想要干什么
thinks you're doing here.
我也不知道  本
I don't know, Ben.
大家都在这里干什么呢？
What are any of us doing here anyway?
这里是我的家
Well, I belong here, you know.
我帮忙建设了这个城镇  我父亲协助它成长
I helped build this town. My father helped it grow.
创办学校
You know, created schools...
修葺公园、铺设道路…
repaired parks, paved streets...
直到他锒铛入狱  对吧？
That was before he went to prison, I'm assuming.
这是个…复杂的故事
It is a complicated story.
但我不是来探讨我的家族史的
But I'm not here to talk about my family's history.
我有个疑问
I actually have a question.
虽然油管不断地删除这个视频  但我还是找到它了
They keep taking this off YouTube, but I tracked it down.
不管怎样  这就是互联网的德性
You know, anyhow, it is the fucking Internet.
我反复看了无数遍
And I keep watching it over and over again.
有件事我始终想不明白
And there's just one thing I don't get.
视频中的你正在跟某人对打
Here you are, fighting this guy.
他是你的朋友  对吧？
He's your friend, right?
我是这么听说的
That's what I heard, that he was your friend.
他是你的朋友  然而接下来却发生了这一幕
And then this happens, right here.
没错  他输了
Yeah, he's done.
谁都看得出来  谢谢
Everybody can see. Thank you.
就在此时
Right here.
砰！
Bam!
看到最后一拳了吗？就是这一拳
See that last hit? That's the one...
在我看来  就是这一拳
In my opinion, that's the one...
要了他的命
that did it.
毫无疑问是那一拳
That was definitely the one that did it.
是的
It was.
所以我的问题是…
So, I guess my question is...
为什么？
Why?
不可能只是因为好胜心  对吧？你…
Right? It can't be just some competitive thing, you...
你都已经赢了
you've won the fight.
可以收手了
You can back off now.
但你…你没有收手
But you... you don't.
只是去…
You just keep...
一拳接一拳地打下
punching and punching and punching.
为什么？
So, why?
为什么不停下来？
Why don't you just stop?
♪ I'm gonna go out dancing every night ♪
♪ I'm gonna see all the city lights ♪
♪ I'm gonna do everything With silver and gold ♪
♪ I've got to hurry up Before I grow too old ♪
祝你晚安
You have a good night.
♪ I'm gonna take a trip All around the world ♪
♪ I'm gonna kiss all the pretty girls ♪
♪ I'm gonna do everything With silver and gold ♪
♪ I've got to hurry up Before I grow too old ♪
给他们一点教训  越惨痛越好
Make it hurt as much as possible.
烧掉这里也无妨
You can burn the place down.
嘿  你这身西装不错嘛
Hey, nice suit.
看起来活像复活节的龌龊皮条客
You look like a shitty pimp on Easter.
你的品味总是那么差
Then again, you always had bad taste.
谢谢  这可是名师定制款  弗兰基  我特地去意大利定制的
Thank you. It's Cleopini, Frankie. I went to Italy to get it fucking fitted.
大老远买来的衣服  依然丑得像坨狗屎
It's a long way to go to still look like dog shit.
到我店里来做什么？
- God. - What are you doin' at my place?
-不关你的事
None of your goddamn business.
-你到我店里来做什么？
What are you doin' at my place?
-我想做什么就做什么
Anything I fucking want.
真的  -是吗？
- That's the truth. - Oh, really?
好了  兄弟们  动手吧
All right, lads. Let's go.
-离我的车窗远一点  -去你的！
- Get out of my goddamn window! - Fuck you!
好久没在夜店尽情挥杆了
It's been a while since I've been clubbin'.
♪ 来吧 ♪
♪ Yeah, come on ♪
♪ 来吧  伙计们 ♪
♪ Come on, boys ♪
♪ 我爱你…- ♪
♪ I love ya, I love ya ♪
跟我想的一样
Just what I thought.
这家路边餐馆现在是我的了
This roadhouse is mine.
♪ 临走前再喝一杯  小子 ♪
♪ One shot for my get on boy ♪
♪ 然后把猪排吐出来 ♪
♪ Roll up the pork chop ♪
嘿  伙计们
Hey, fellas.
看来今晚是个“狂”欢夜！
Looks like you're havin' a smashing night!
♪ 临走前再给我舔一下  小子 ♪
♪ One lick for my get on boy ♪
♪ 他吃腻的猪排 ♪
♪ Pork chop got sick ♪
♪ 临走前再给我舔两下  小子 ♪
♪ Yeah, two lick for my get on boy ♪
嘿  美女
Hey, beautiful.
-我叫诺克斯  -嗨
- I'm Knox. - Howdy.
一起跳个舞吧
Let's dance.
嘿！这是我的女人  兄弟  你要干什么？
Hey! That's my fucking girl, bro. What are you doin'?
去你的
Fuck, man!
我喜欢这首歌  宝贝  你不喜欢吗？
I love this song, baby. Don't you?
也许吧
I guess.
♪ 当你打开收音机时 ♪
♪ When you turn on your radio dial ♪
♪ 里面放的全是狗屎  不是吗？ ♪
♪ It's just the drink in me ♪
♪ 还我正反两面  金曲满载的45号黑胶唱片 ♪
♪ Bring back the 45 vinyl with the double-A flip side ♪
♪ 临走前再喝一杯  小子 ♪
♪ One shot for my get on, boy ♪
♪ 猪排怎么了 ♪
♪ What's up with pork chop ♪
我讨厌这首歌！
I hate this song!
-你好啊  乐队  -滚开
- Hello, band. - Back up.
给我冷静点！
Hey, calm the fuck down!
嘿
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
伙计  我们何不到外面…
Man, why don't we just take it outside...
该死的！
Fuck!
不要啊！-
Hey, hey, don't do it!
酒吧大乱斗！
Bar fight!
♪ 临走前再给我舔一下  小子 ♪
♪ One lick for my get on boy ♪
♪ 他吃腻的猪排 ♪
♪ Pork chop got sick ♪
♪ 临走前再给我舔两下  小子 ♪
♪ Two lick for my get on boy ♪
天啊！-
Oh, my God!
王八蛋！
Motherfucker!
道尔顿！
Dalton!
行了…
All right.
嘿  兄弟  见到你真好
Oh, hey, man. Good to see you.
道尔顿！
Dalton!
干吗？
What?
你总算现身了
It's about fuckin' time.
干架啊
That's what!
你很清楚我是他们特地派来
You know, I got sent here special.
收拾你的
Just for you.
你把你的朋友全都带来了？
But you brought all your friends with you?
我想你可能会怀念有观众的日子
I thought you might miss havin' an audience.
我只是想尽量考虑得周到些
I was trying to be thoughtful.
就像按次付费收看一样
Like on pay-per-view.
支付25英镑
25 quid.
就能看我打烂你的脸！
Watch me pulp your face!
看来我要输了
Well, I guess I'm gonna lose, then.
别这么沮丧嘛
Don't be like that.
来  我给你一个忠告
Here. I've got a tip for ya.
别让任何人靠得这么近
Don't let no one get this close.
这才像样嘛
There he is.
世界上最臭名昭著的拳手道尔顿
The world's most notorious fighter, Dalton.
来吧  握个手
Put'er there.
你心理有问题
There's something wrong with you.
我也是
Me, too.
德克斯  你还是不是警察  我们需要援助！
Dex, this is serious! Are you a cop or what? We need help!
我已经派了两辆警车过去  仁至义尽了  艾莉
I sent two cars already, El. It's the best I could do.
道尔顿
Dalton. Dalton.
嘿  你没事吧？
Hey! Are you okay?
艾莉  比利受了很严重的伤
Ellie! Billy's really hurt.
艾莉！
Ellie!
没事的，坐下  操！-
- Come on, it's okay. Sit down. - Fuck!
他把他搞得一团糟-
He fucked him up really bad.
我在呢！怎么啦？那家伙用高尔夫球杆打了他
- I'm here. What happened? - Hit him with the golf club.
那个爱尔兰混蛋打断了我的背-
That Irish fuck broke my back.
操-
Fuck.
嘿  你这是要走了吗？
Hey. What, are you leaving?
你可真会开玩笑  弗兰基
You're a funny one, Frankie.
好吧  没错
Okay. I mean, yeah...
我知道我没有向你坦白一切  好吗？
I know I wasn't totally honest with you, all right?
布兰特想夺走我的路边餐馆
Brandt wants to take the Road House away from me.
看到那边了吗？公路沿线那些建筑
You see that? All up and down the highway?
全被布兰特买下来了
Brandt owns all of that.
他想铲平那里
And he wants to level it and...
给一群有钱的混蛋建一个狗屁度假村
build some bullshit resort for a bunch of rich assholes.
为此他需要路边餐馆的地皮  但我不会让他得逞的
And he needs the Road House to do it. But I'm not gonna let that happen.
现在就剩我一个坚守阵地了
I'm the last holdout, man.
那你应该继续坚守阵地
You should keep holdin' out.
嘿  布兰特没钱了
Hey. Brandt's out of money.
他在跟一群可疑的家伙借钱
And he's borrowing from shady guys.
到时候他要是还不上
And when he doesn't pay them back...
他们定会宰了他
they're gonna fucking end him.
去他的  我不在乎
All right, well, fuck that guy.
什么意思  你这是要走了吗？
So, what? You're leaving now?
弗兰基  我从一开始就告诉过你
Frankie, I told you from the jump...
你应该雇用另一个人
you should've hired that other guy.
他们把你吓跑了？
They scared you off?
-你就那么害怕吗？
Are you really that afraid?
-是的  我很害怕
Yes, I am afraid.
那是你永远无法理解的恐惧
More than you could ever understand.
事情出了点岔子  本先生
Things didn't exactly go to plan, Mr. B.
诺克斯没有干掉那名保镖
Knox didn't kill the bouncer.
我们的人几乎都受了重伤
Most of our guys are pretty banged up.
加上赶到现场的警察  不是我们的人  所以…
Also, the wrong cops showed at the Road House, so...
大鸡哥也帮不上忙
Big Dick can't help us there.
玻璃岛度假村
您想让我怎么做？
What do you want me to do?
去厨房帮我再拿一瓶酒来
I want you to get me another bottle from the galley.
嘿  那里面不安全
Hey, it's not safe in there.
那个小女孩在哪儿？  那个小女孩和她的父亲
Where's the little girl? That little girl and her father.
救护车把他们送去医院了
Ambulance took 'em to the hospital.
赶紧离开那里
Now get out of there!
我怎么没听到汽车声
I didn't hear a car.
我是走路过来的
Yeah, well, I walked.
从书店一路走来
From the bookstore.
-看来你收到我们的警告了？
So, you got our little message?
-确实收到了
I sure did.
那是你的主意吗？
Was that your idea?
没错  那小女孩挺可爱的
Yeah, she's a cute girl.
有点固执
She's kinda stubborn.
有点像你
Bit like you.
知道吗
You know...
说来好笑…
the funny thing is...
我原本已经要走了
I was already leaving.
我们终于吓跑你了？
We finally scared you off, huh?
不完全是
Uh, not exactly.
只要你害怕就行
Just as long as you're scared.
我刚刚打断了你的舌骨
I just broke the hyoid bone in your throat.
可能连气管也一并打断了
Probably also collapsed your trachea.
不管怎样  你都不能呼吸了
Either way, you won't be able to breathe anymore.
说来奇怪  今天另一个人也问了我是否害怕
You know, it's strange. Somebody else asked me if I was afraid today.
我确实很害怕
I am afraid.
害怕自己被你这种人渣逼急了
I'm afraid of what happens when somebody pushes me too far.
后果会不堪设想
Somebody just like you.
因为我很清楚接下来会发生什么
'Cause I know what happens next.
见鬼了  好吧
Oh, fuck. Okay.
嘿  老兄
Hey. Hey, man.
他看起来挺重的
Wow, he looks heavy.
真厉害
Good for you. Um...
那个  其实我正准备…  我正准备离开
Hey, man, I was just... I was just leaving...
再也不回来了
you know, for good.
事实证明  这些家伙
Turns out these guys...
并不像我刚开始想的那么好
not as nice as I thought they were initially.
我只是喜欢骑摩托车
I just like riding motorcycles, man...
但在南佛罗里达州  不加入帮派的话很难混下去
but it's really hard to do in South Florida without a group.
老兄
Hey, man.
你应该不会杀我吧？
You're not gonna kill me or anything, right?
布兰特在哪里？
Where's Brandt?
实不相瞒  他们很少告诉我这些事情
Okay, I'm gonna be honest with you, man. They don't tell me much. You know.
我每次都是最后一个知道
Kinda the last one to find out about everything...
处境挺尴尬的
which is kinda weird position to be in.
不过我无意中听到了  布兰特手下的对话
But I overheard some of Brandt's guys talking and...
我想他们会在丰收岛碰头
I guess there's a meeting at Harvest Key.
布兰特会去取一笔钱  用来做某件事
Brandt's getting some of the money that he needs for something.
时间是凌晨五点
It's at 5:00 a.m.
我想这碰头时间有点早  对吧？
Which I think is early for a meeting. Am I right?
好的
Okay.
回头见  谢谢你这次没有使用暴力
I'll see you. Thank you for no more violence.
祝你抛尸顺利
Good luck with the guy.
冰块
让他走-
Let him go.
滚开！停下-
- Fuck off! - Stop!
够了！停下-
That's enough! Stop!
没问题  可以了
All right, all right, we're good.
你想计数吗？-
You wanna count it?
嘿！
Hey!
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey, you're awake.
-我的船
My boat.
-对  你们警长的船要少一艘了
Yeah. You're gonna be short one sheriff's boat.
抱歉
Sorry.
天啊！你刚刚杀了他吗？
Jesus! Did you just kill him?
不
Oh, no.
他早就死了  我在数小时之前就杀了他
He's already dead. I killed him hours ago.
-那是我的枪吗？
Is that my gun?
-没错  是你的枪
Yep, sure is.
等等  你没必要这么做
Wait. You don't have to do this.
我也不想走到这一步
I wish I didn't.
但我生气了
But I'm angry.
虽然我轻易不生气  但一旦生气起来
It takes a lot to get me angry, but when I am...
就没有善罢甘休一说  我也想停下来
I just can't let go. I wish I could...
但…  你们老大和布兰特真的让我很恼火
but your boss and Brandt really pissed me off.
他们会发现他并非死于枪杀的
They'll know those bullets didn't kill him.
这只是为了误导他们
It'll just confuse 'em.
我会告诉他们是你干的
I'll tell 'em it was you.
好吧
Oh, okay!
不过无所谓
You know what though?
反正你十有八九会想不起来这一切
There's a real possibility you won't remember any of this anyway.
等等  你说什么？
Wait, wait, what?
当你像我一样在拳击界打滚多年
When you've been fighting as long as I have,
你就会知道脑震荡的威力
you know the power of a concussion.
重重的一击  真的可以让你
- Wait. - A real whack can really knock...
失去短期记忆
the short-term memory out of ya.
记忆需要几分钟
Something about how it takes a memory...
才能到达大脑的长期记忆区
a couple of minutes to get to the long-term part of your brain.
我们才聊了一分半钟左右
I don't know. Anyway, you and I have only been talking for about a minute and half.
我没听懂你的意思
I don't understand.
那边是什么？
What's that over there?
你好  我是海岸警卫队的  威廉姆斯上士
Hello, this is Coast Guard Chief Petty Officer Williams.
有什么能帮到你？
How can I help you?
嗨  我想我应该告诉你
Yes, hi. I just thought you should know that there's a dead body...
有一具尸体和一名可疑的副警长  被困在了丰收岛上
and a suspicious sheriff's deputy stranded on Harvest Key.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
你最好赶紧过去  因为我已经通知了当地媒体
Yeah, you'll need to get there quick 'cause I already called the local news.
能否告诉我  你的名字和回拨号码  以备…
Can I get a name and callback number just in case we get...
警长
Sheriff.
我只是想谈谈
I just wanna talk.
你又来抓我了？
Are you here to arrest me again?
道尔顿  听着  艾莉出事了
Dalton, listen. It's Ellie.
他们抓走了她
They have her.
她现在在布兰特手上
Brandt's got her.
他想要回他的钱  你拿走的那些钱
Wants his money. The money you took.
我没有拿任何钱
I didn't take any money.
我的副手都告诉我了
My deputy told me.
说你讲了一堆短期记忆之类的鬼话
You were talking some shit about short-term memory.
糟糕
Shit.
没错  是我拿走了钱
Yeah, I did take it.
你必须把钱还给他
You need to give it back to him.
你…  你跟他说钱是我拿走的？
Right, you told him I took it?
这不重要  反正他都会怪罪于我
It doesn't matter. He blames me anyway.
他认为我在撒谎
He thinks I'm lying.
因为负责处理那笔钱的人是我的副手
It was my deputy in charge of the goddamn money.
你还在乎我女儿的话  就帮我把她救回来
If my daughter means anything to you, you'll help me get her back.
道尔顿  听着
Dalton, listen.
他说要在中午之前看到钱  不然就会杀了她
He wants the money by noon, or he says he'll kill her.
我相信他真的会这么做
I believe him.
请帮帮我
Please help me.
好吧
Okay.
谢天谢地  赶紧把钱带上
Oh, thank God. Let's get the money...
钱不在这里
It's not here.
多久才能拿到？
How long will it take?
不知道  我把它藏了起来  需要一点时间
I don't know. I hid it. It's gonna take a while.
我们在哪里会合？
Where should I meet you?
我最喜欢擦拭我的船了
I like polishing my boat.
对我来说  最开心的事情莫过于  看到它光亮如新…
Nothing makes me happier than to see it all shiny and...
稍等  我回头再打给你  该死的  嘿！
Oh, hold on, I'll call you back. Shit. Hey!
你在干什么？
Fuck you doing, man?
-太好了  你来了  -那是我的船  给我下来！
- That's my boat, buddy. Get off! - Great, you're here.
你想必就是那位前男友  我在找钥匙
You must be the ex-boyfriend. I'm just looking for the key.
艾莉叫我来拿船
Ellie told me to come get the boat.
原来在这里  找到了！
Here they are. Bingo!
你就是那个混蛋保镖吧？
You're that bouncer asshole, aren't you?
对  我就是那个混蛋保镖
Yes, I am that "bouncer asshole."
看到这个了吗？  我可是警察  你个白痴
You see this right here, pal? I'm a cop, you idiot.
放心吧  我马上就会把它开回来
Don't worry. I'll bring it right back.
不行  你哪儿都别想去
No. Hey, you're not goin' anywhere, man.
嘿！
Hey!
你有麻烦了  给我回来
You're in trouble. Back it up.
没事的  我几个小时后就回来  好吗？
It's fine. I'll be back in a couple hours, all right?
一点都不好
Nothing is fine about this.
好吧  你有两个小时的时间
Okay. Okay. You got two hours.
给我毫发无损地把它带回来  听到了吗？
Bring that back without a scratch on her, you got it?
有一点划痕都不行
Not one scratch.
拜托  这是在水上  怎么会弄到划痕？
Come on, it's water. How am I gonna get a scratch on it?
超级安全驾校
教练车
让我来看看这是怎么回事
All right. Let's see what this is about.
人都死哪去了？
Where the fuck is everyone?
有劳了
Thank you, sir.
过来
Come here.
钱不在船上
Money's not on the boat, if that's what you're looking for.
是吗？
Oh, yeah?
你应该把钱带过来的
Man, you were supposed to bring the money with you.
这下布兰特要失望了
Brandt's gonna be disappointed.
没关系  我会告诉他是你拿走了钱
That's okay. I'll just tell him you took it.
是吗？
Oh, yeah?
走吧
Let's go.
这家伙
Oh, this guy.
这船真不错
Nice boat.
-看起来很贵的样子  -是很贵
- Looks expensive. - Yeah.
这船以前是我老爸的
It used to be my old man's.
他离开后  我就继承了它
I got it when he went away.
连同他欠下的所有人情
Along with all his obligations...
和所有债务
all his debts.
所以
So, yeah.
确实挺贵的
It's fuckin' expensive.
说起钱
Speaking of which,
我的钱呢？
where's my goddamn money?
我把钱交给他了
Oh, I gave it to him.
-你个混蛋  -嘿  冷静点
- You fucker! - Hey, calm down.
山姆
Sam.
你为什么要一直浪费我的时间？
Why do you keep wasting my time?
说真的  我都告诉你  那女孩命悬一线了
Honestly, you were told the girl's life depended on it.
所以我的钱呢？
So, where's my fucking money?
我没看到艾莉在这里
I don't see Ellie anywhere.
而且这家伙看起来悠然自得
And this guy looks pretty comfortable for a guy
完全不像女儿被人绑架了
who just had his daughter kidnapped.
根本没有绑架一事  蠢货
There's no kidnapping, dumb-ass.
一场骗局
Ohh! A double-cross.
你还真相信本绑架我女儿了？
You actually believed that Ben took my daughter?
我们可是合作伙伴  白痴
We are partners, idiot.
关于这点  我确实绑走了她
Yeah, about that. I did kinda take her.
-什么？  -双重骗局
- What? - Another double-cross.
-这是怎么回事  本？
What the fuck, Ben?
-劝你别这么做
I wouldn't do that.
大鸡哥  坐下
Big Dick, sit down.
给我坐下！
Sit the fuck down!
我怎么知道你是否可信？
How was I supposed to know I could trust you, huh?
等我拿到了钱  你便可以带走她
Once I get my money, you can have her.
-王八蛋！
Son of a bitch!
-两位  需要给你们一点时间吗？
Boys, do you want me to give you a second?
-嘿…  -够了
- Hey... - Stop.
别闹了
Just stop!
我想建一样东西
I'm trying to build somethin'.
然而你却一再
You keep on pushin' me
挑战我的底线
and just pushin' me.
我简直…该死的  真可笑
And I just... Fuck, it's funny.
那真是…我简直要被气疯了
It's like... I'm just like, "Fuck!"
他太吵了
- He's noisy. - Yes.
对  他确实很吵
He is noisy. He is.
现在我只能让山姆给你一点教训了
Now I'm gonna have to have Sam here hurt you.
-千万别  -我偏要
- Oh, no. Please. - Oh, yes.
-请别这样  -别那样看着我
- Please, no. - Don't look at me like that.
如果这招还是不行  那我就只能拿艾莉开刀了
Now, if that doesn't work, I'll have to get Ellie.
届时情况将会一发不可收拾
And shit will get real crazy, real fast.
-慢着  该死的  等一下！  -住口  坐下
- Hey, wait, goddammit. Wait! - Stop. Sit down.
天啊  又是这该死的疯子
Oh, my God, this fucking psycho again.
别让那疯子上船
Do not let that maniac on the boat.
我倒是知道有个人  会对背叛这件事非常生气
I do know one guy who's gonna be pretty pissed about this whole betrayal thing.
那是谁？
And who is that?
只是某个混蛋警察
Oh, just some asshole cop.
他在干什么？
What the hell is he doing?
糟了
Shit.
他到底在干什么？
What the fuck is he doing?
王八蛋！
Motherfucker!
艾莉！
Ellie? Ellie!
着火了！
Fire!
艾莉！
Ellie!
弃船！
Abandon ship!
艾莉！
Ellie!
嘿！
Hey!
艾莉！
Ellie!
艾莉
Ellie.
嘿  蠢货！
Hey, dickhead!
快离开这艘船
Get off the boat!
-嘿  混蛋！  -小心！
- Hey, asshole! - Watch out!
你死定了！
You're gonna die!
你先走  艾莉  我随后跟上  去吧
Go, Ellie, go. I'll be right behind you. Go.
我他妈的…-
I'm gonna fucking...
见鬼
Oh, fuck.
你挑男朋友的品味真差  艾莉
You got shit taste in boyfriends, El.
-别乱动！  -去你的！
- Don't fucking move! - Fuck you!
我要亲手毁了那该死的路边餐馆
I'll just destroy the fucking Road House myself.
你在这里
There ya are.
我来帮你
Let me help you.
瞧瞧
Lookie here.
-我们的小八角笼  -什么？
- Our own little octagon. - What?
你的几何是谁教的？
Who taught you shapes?
你那该死的男朋友追来了！
Your fucking boyfriend!
我们去接他吧
Let's pick him up.
操你妈！-
You motherfucker!
操！-
Fuck!
天啊！
Jesus.
道尔顿
Dalton.
你想杀了我们？-
You trying to kill us?
不想，走开！-
No. Get off!
艾莉！你总是…-
Ellie! You always...
你真是个白痴！
You're such an idiot!
道尔顿  快跳！
Dalton, come on!
在这等着
Wait here.
天啊-
Oh, God.
居然是鱼叉？
Fucking fishing spear?
成功了-
I'm done! I'm done!
停下-
Let's stop.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
我不玩了
I'm done.
该死的
Shit.
你摔断了我的鼻梁
You broke my fuckin' nose.
我为之努力的一切…
Everything I fuckin' worked for...
因为一个该死的保镖  全都付诸东流了！
all gone because of a fucking bouncer!
见鬼
Shit.
看来我弄伤你的腿了
Looks like I fucked up your leg.
你的开车技术太烂了
You're a shit driver.
靠右行驶  不太习惯
Wrong side of the road.
友善点
Be nice.
这架钢琴跑调了
This piano is out of tune.
我听着挺好的
Sounds pretty good to me.
你现在就要杀了我吗？
You gonna kill me now?
还是必须先和我成为朋友？
I thought we had to be friends first.
杀了他！
Kill him!
快杀了他
Fucking joke.
动手啊！
Do it!
做你该做的事！
Do your fucking job!
怎样才能让你闭嘴？
What does it take to shut you up?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你该走了  道尔顿
It's time for you to go, Dalton.
你从未来过这里
You were never here.
我会帮你善后的
I got you covered.
你走吧
Go.
你必须离开这里
You have to go.
好吧
Okay.
不算太糟糕
It's not so bad.
对  还能修复
Yeah, no, it's fixable.
-绝对可以  -对
- Definitely. - Yep.
还能修复  这…
It's fixable. This is...
-还能修复？  -对
-"Fixable"? - Yep.
-酒吧里有辆卡车
There's a truck in the bar.
-这…确实没错
That is correct.
但只要清理掉这些东西  我们再…
But as soon as this is clear and we...
好好收拾一番
Little elbow grease.
就会完好如初
It's gonna be good as new.
请务必小心那河豚
Watch out for the pufferfish, please.
-来吧  赶紧干活  -嘿
- Come on, move it. - Hey.
-什么事？  -你们今天开门营业吗？
- Yeah? - Are you guys open today?
当然了  本店永远开门迎客
Yeah. We're always open.
走吧-
Let's go.
翻过来
Swing around.
我来拿一下这个
Let me get this.
嘿
Hey.
这就结束了？你就这样…
So, this is it? You're just gonna...
你就这样迎着日落  策马远行了？
You're just gonna ride off into the sunset?
故事的结局不都这样吗？
That's always how the story ends, right?
不  并非总是如此
No, not always.
有时候主角会留下来
Sometimes the hero stays and...
打造属于自己的小家
makes his own little homestead.
我想这个故事的主角并不是我  查莉
I don't think I'm the hero in this particular story, Charlie.
你也许不是主角
So, maybe you're not the hero.
但我可以告诉你
I got news for you.
你也不是反派
You ain't the villain either.
查莉！
Charlie!
-你没事吧？  -没事
- You good? - Yeah, I'm good.
-别闹了  伙计  -你最好保持警惕
- Shut up, man. - You better stay on your toes.
-不管他走没走  -闭嘴
- Don't matter if he gone. - Shut up.
来啊  你个娘娘腔！
Come on, you pussy!
拦住那个人！
Stop that man!
新威龙杀阵